Okay, we have a word document here that
looks to be structured well with a nice
big font here. Bookshare mobile uh app
and below that download the Bookshare
reader which also looks like it's an uh
a like a heading too um slightly smaller
bolded text size and then below that
really small um
text here as a paragraph and then below
that signing in which looks like another
uh heading two and then it continues on.
So let's bring our cursor to the first
item uh Bookshare mobile app and click
on the the home styles and we can see
that oh the it is not a heading one it's
actually normal style. So we can move
over and click on the heading one and
now it's a heading one. It actually
changed the color, the font and the
size. We can change this back to
whatever we want. make it like you know
26 point uh change the color if you want
etc. The next one here download the
Bookshare mobile uh Bookshare reader app
looks to be also a heading. Let's take a
look and go to the home styles again and
again it's normal and we want it to be a
heading too. You can also
just use like the said the keyboard
shortcut and Ctrl Alt and then the
number two automatically brings this to
um to the uh heading level two. Uh the
next text here is really small. I'm
going to select that entire paragraph.
And then if I go up to the uh the font
and the size, I see that it's currently
an eightoint font. That's kind of a
an eight point font. That's kind of a
little small. We'll actually make it
like uh 12 or you know 16 18. We'll make
it 16 point font. That should be good
here. And again signing in looks like a
heading too but when I click on the
styles it's actually still normal. And
we'll double we'll go over here to
heading two. Make that a heading two.
And we're now good to go.